# **Ali Gunes**

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/ali-gunes

**GitHub:** www.github.com/AliGunez **Email:** a.gunes.office@gmail.com

Mobile: +44 7445252776

I am a Software Engineering student at HyperionDev, skilled in Python, SQL, object-oriented programming, systems analysis, and design. I earned a BA (Hons) in Games Art and Design from Norwich University of the Arts. I have experience in creating ecommerce websites, 3D asset design and development, CAD modelling, and 3D printing.

# **Education**

HyperionDev, 2023 – current
Software Engineering
Norwich University of the Arts, 2015 – 2019
BA (Hons) Games Art and Design

## **Technical Skills**

- Software development in Python
- Object oriented programming
- Systems analysis
- Systems design
- 3D Asset creation

# **Employment history**

### Embassy of gold LTD, Hertfordshire

Company Director, October 2020 - Current

- Creation and maintenance of ecommerce website including product imagery and all written content.
- Design and development of 3D assets; ready to be 3D printed, cast and finished.
- Operation of resin 3D printing, production of prototypes and final, cast ready prints.
- Polishing, cleaning and finishing final jewellery pieces.
- Directing all other operational aspects of the business.

## MyMiniFactory (3DC LTD Merger), London

AM CAD Specialist, October 2022 – March 2023

- Repairing and improving customers CAD models ready for production.
- Assisting clients with CAD issues and developing fixes for common problems.
- Assisting in development of production pipeline with emphasis on CAD solutions.
- Assisting manufacturing team wherever needed.

### 3DC LTD, London

**3D Printer assistant, March 2022 – October 2022** 

- Creating CAD builds ready for printers.
- General maintenance of 3D printers.
- Setup of prints and removal of finished 3D models.
- Assisting in development of production pipeline.
- Repairing and improving customers CAD models ready for production.
- Post processing and fulfilment of customer orders.

#### **3DC LTD,** London

Intern ZBrush Artist, February 2020 – August 2020

- Created final print-ready 3D models from clients requests and personally conceptualized designs.
- Troubleshooting, Remodelling and development of existing 3D assets to final production ready models.
- Developed a body of documents including best practices, workflow and troubleshooting methods for future 3D artist interns.

### References

#### **Matthew Baca**

MyMiniFactory; Head of manufacturing

Email: <a href="mb@3dcltd.com">mb@3dcltd.com</a>
Tel: +44 7757 859134

#### **Bernat Santaeugenia**

MyMiniFactory; Head of manufacturing

Email: <u>bs@3dcltd.com</u> Tel: +34 671 38 85 67